嘿      嘿
Hey        Hey
琼还好吗      跟她分手了
So how was Joan?        Broke up with her
哦 为什么
Oh, why?
别跟哥说是因为她鼻孔太大了
Don't tell me. Because of the big nostril thing?
真的超大
They were huge.
她打喷嚏的时候 蝙蝠都能飞出来
When she sneezed, bats flew out of them.
得了吧 没那么大啦
Come on, they were not that huge.
真的 她仰头的时候 我都能看到她的脑子
I'm tellin' you, she leaned back, I could see her brain.
你还要甩掉多少完美的异性
How many perfectly fine women are you gonna reject
只是因为这些鸡毛蒜皮的事
over the most superficial insignificant things?
等等 这次我要站在钱德这一边
Hold it. Hold it. I mean, I gotta side with Chandler on this one.
我刚搬到这里的时候
When I first moved to the city
我和一个女孩约会过几次
I went out a couple of times with this girl,
身材超棒 吻技超赞
really hot, great kisser...
可是 她的喉结超大
but, she had the biggest Adam's apple.
哥实在受不了了
It made me nuts.
你来还是我来      我来吧
You or me?        I got it.
乔伊 女人是没有喉结的
Joey, women don't have Adam's apples.
你们在耍我吧
You guys are messing with me, right?
对 没错
Yeah. We are.
这次不赖啊 差一点哥就上当了
That's a good one. For a second there, I was like, whoa!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第03集
海先生之死 The One Where Mr Heckles Dies
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：yjchandler
那么，你说哪个女人
So, you name one woman
是你以正常理由甩掉的
that you broke up with for an actual real reason.
玛琳摩丝拉
Maureen Rasillo.
她不讨厌雅尼可不算是正常理由
'Cause she doesn't hate Yanni is not a real reason.
你好 黑考斯先生
Hello, Mr.Heckles.
你们又来了
You're doing it again.
我们什么都没做啊
We're not doing anything.
你们在跺脚 吵到我的鸟了
You're stomping. It's disturbing my birds.
你又没有养鸟
You don't have birds.
我当然可以养鸟
I could have birds.
好吧 我们会尽量小声      谢谢
Okay, Mr.Heckles, we'll try to keep it down.        Thank you.
我要回去享受我的晚宴了
I'm going to rejoin my dinner party.
好吧 拜拜
All right, bye-bye.
好吧 珍妮丝 就说珍妮丝好了
Okay, Janice, Janice. You gotta give me Janice.
这总不能算挑三拣四了吧
That wasn't about being picky.
对，珍妮丝确实不算
Yeah, We'll give you Janice.
不过我挺怀念她的
I miss Janice, though.
"哈喽 钱德宾!"
"Hello, Chandler Bing!"
"我了个天啊!"
"Oh, my God!"
"噢 钱德"
"Oh Chandler"
"快! 快!"
"Now! Now!"
"就是这样"
"That's it."
"对! 再快点!"
"There! Faster!"
别拿扫帚捅我们了! 我们没有制造噪音!
Stop with the broom! We're not making noise!
我们赢了
We won.
我们真的赢了!      喔噢!
We do! We won!        Whoo!
哦不 黑考斯先生
Oh, Mr.Heckles.
这是怎么回事啊      当时他一定是在扫地
How did this happen?        He musta been sweepin'.
他们发现他的时候还拿着扫把
They found a broom in his hand.
噢 不 天呐
Oh, dear God.
太悲剧了      是啊
That's terrible.        I know.
昨天我也有扫地
I was sweeping yesterday.
搞不好我也会挂
It coulda been me.
是啊 扫地而已 真是没想到
Sure, sweeping. You never know.
世事难料啊
Never know.
好吧 虽然很微弱 但我还是感到他还在这栋楼里
Okay, it's very faint, but I can still sense him in the building.
奔向天堂吧 黑考斯先生
Go into the light, Mr.Heckles!
好了 菲比
Okay, Phoebe.
抱歉 不过有时候他们需要指引
I'm sorry, but sometimes they need help.
哦      又来了
Yeah.        Here we go.
没关系 你们尽管嘲笑我
That's fine, go ahead and scoff.
但是 这个世界上我也有很多东西不相信
But, you know, there're a lot of things out there I don't believe in
可并不代表它们不是真的
but that doesn't mean they're not true.
比如?
Such as?
比如麦田怪圈 百慕大三角 进化论
Like crop circles, or the Bermuda Triangle, or evolution.
喔噢 喔噢 喔噢
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
什么 你不相信进化论?
What, you don't... you don't believe in evolution?
是啊 不怎么信
No. Not really.
你不相信进化论?
You don't believe in evolution?
我不知道 只是...
I don't know. It's just, you know...
猴子啦 达尔文啦 故事是不赖
monkeys, Darwin, you know, it's a, it's a nice story.
我只是觉得有点儿太简单了
I just think it's a little too easy.
太简单? 太...
Too easy? Too...
地球上所有生物的进化过程
The process of every living thing on this planet
从单细胞生物开始千百万年的进化
evolving over millions of years from single-celled organisms
太简单了?
is, is too easy?
对 我就是不相信这套理论
Yeah, I just don't buy it.
抱歉 进化论不在于你信或不信 菲比
Excuse me. Evolution is not for you to buy, Phoebe.
进化论是科学事实 就像我们所呼吸的空气
Evolution is scientific fact, like, like the air we breathe
就像地心引力
like gravity.
别惹我开始谈地心引力
Okay,don't get me started on gravity.
你... 你不相信地心引力?
You uh, you don't believe in gravity?
好吧 我并不是完全不信
Well,it's not so much that, you know, like I don't believe in it.
只是我近来觉得...
You know, it's just... lately I get the feeling that...
我不是被引力拉住 而是被什么东西压住了
I'm not so much being pulled down as I am being pushed.
被压住?
Pushed?
啊哦 牛顿来了 而且他很火大
Uh-oh. It's Isaac Newton, and he's pissed.
她在这儿 还有另外那个 就在那边
There she is. And over there, that's the other one.
这位是巴迪先生 黑考斯的律师 他要跟你们谈谈
This is Mr.Buddy Boyle, Heckles' attorney He'd like to talk to you.
我们能帮什么忙?
What can we do for you?
好了 孩子们 情况是这样
All right, kids, here's the deal.
根据我客户的遗嘱
According to my client's will
他想把他所有的资产留给
he wants to leave all his earthly possessions...
"住在我公寓上方吵人的女孩们"
to "The noisy girls in the apartment above mine."
他的家人呢?
What about his family?
他没有家人      噢
He didn't have any.        Whoa.
好吧 那我们来谈谈钱的问题
Okay, so let's talk money.
好吧 一个子儿都没有
All right, there was none.
现在 我们来签字
Now, let's talk signing.
你是吵闹女孩一号 你是吵闹女孩二号
You be noisy girl number one. You be noisy girl number two.
简直不敢相信 我们居然一直以为他痛恨我们
I can't believe that this whole time we thought he hated us.
这真是不可思议 能对别人的一生有如此大的触动
I mean, isn't it amazing how much you can touch someone's life
自己却浑然不觉?
without even knowing it?
你们看看这堆垃圾
Would you look at this dump?
他确实痛恨我们! 这是他的终极大复仇!
He hated us! This was his final revenge!
谁曾见过这么多垃圾!
Have you ever seen so much crap!
事实上 我认为这间公寓玷污了垃圾的美名
Actually, I think this apartment sullies the good name of crap.
快看这个
Check this out.
这个可以给我吗?
Can I have this?
你怎么能不相信进化论?
How can you not believe in evolution?
我不知道 就是不信吧 瞧这件怪异的衬衫!
I don't know, just don't. Look at this funky shirt!
菲比 拜托 我整个成年生涯都在研究进化论
Pheebs, I've studied evolution my entire adult life. Okay?
我们从全球各地搜集化石
And I can tell you, we've collected fossils from all over the world
事实证明了不同物种的进化
that actually show the evolution of different species. Okay?
我是说 你真的可以看到这些物种
I mean, you can, you can literally see them
经历了时间的进化
evolving through time.
真的? 你真的看得到?
Really? You can actually see it?
千真万确 美国 中国 非洲 全世界都有
You bet! In the U.S., China, Africa, all over!
好吧 我原先不知道
See, I didn't know that.
行 现在知道了吧
Well, there you go.
哼
Huh.
真正的问题在于
So now the real question is,
是谁把那些化石放在那里的 又是为了什么
who put those fossils there and why?
嘿 瞧这个 "我的牢骚大合集"
Hey, look at this, "My Big Book of Grievances"
嘿 那是我
Hey, there's me.
"4月17日 噪音过大"
"April 17th, excessive noise"
"意大利佬带了个妞儿回家
"Italian guy comes home with a date." Yeah.
钱德你看 也有你
Chandler, you're in here too.
"4月18日 噪音过大"
"April 18th, excessive noise"
"意大利佬的基佬室友带干洗衣物回家"
"Italian guy's gay roommate brings home dry cleaning."
真是太好了
Well,that's excellent.
摩妮卡 瞧这盏灯
Monica, Monica, look at this lamp.
这俗不俗气 这个我们一定要带回去
Is this tacky or what? We have to have this.
瑞秋 我想我们一般的灯已经够多了
Rache, I think we have enough regular lamps.
什么? 拜托 我又不是
What? Oh, Come on,I mean it's not, it's not like
想要这个娃娃型的钟或什么的
I'm asking for this girlie clock or anything.
当然 我觉得这个也很酷
Which, by the way, I also think is really cool.
喂 这跟我的东西都不搭啊
Look, it doesn't go with any of my stuff.
那我的东西呢
Well, what about my stuff?
你什么东西都没有
You don't have any stuff.
你还是认为那是你一个人的公寓 对吧
You still think of it as your apartment, don't you?
呃 不是      是的 你还这么认为
Mmm... No.        Yes, you do.
你认为那是你一个人的公寓
You think of it as your apartment
我只是个租房的
and I'm just someone who rents a room.
呃...
Mmm...
好吧 你就继续支支吾吾吧
Okay, while you "Mmm" on that for awhile
我要找个地方放我的新台灯了
I'm gonna go find a place for my new lamp.
好 菲比 看到我是如何摆弄这些小玩意儿的吗?
Okay, Pheebs. See how I'm making these little toys move?
相互对称的拇指!
Opposable thumbs!
若非进化论 你如何解释相互对称的拇指
Without evolution, how do you explain opposable thumbs?
也许外星舰长需要拇指才能驾驶他们的太空飞船
Maybe the Overlords needed them to steer their spacecrafts.
麻烦告诉我你是在开玩笑
Please tell me you're joking.
这样说好了 你相信某事但我不信
Look, can't we just say that you believe in something and I don't?
不 菲比 不可以 因为       有何不可?
No. No, no, Pheebs, we can't, ok? Because...       Why not?
为什么非要每个人都认同你的看法
What is this obsessive need you have to make everybody agree with you?
到底是为什么 你知道我怎么想吗
No, what's that all about? You know what I think?
我想是时候你该好好检视下"罗斯"这个生物了
I think maybe it's time you put "Ross" under the microscope.
我的耳朵在喷血吗
Is there blood coming out of my ears?
快看快看 黑考斯的高中纪念册
Check it out, check it out, Heckles high school yearbook.
哇 他看起来很正常
Wow, he looks so normal.
他甚至有点可爱
He's even kind of cute.
"黑考斯 连自然课你都能让我开怀大笑"
"Heckles,you crack me up in science class."
"你是全校最逗的孩子"
"You're the funniest kid in school."
最逗的? 黑考斯?      上面是这么写的
Funniest? Heckles?        That's what it says.
黑考斯被选为班上的活宝 我也是
Wow, Heckles was voted class clown, and so was I.
他说得对 你们听听那噪音
He was right. Would you listen to that?
的确非常吵
I'd call that excessive.
哇哦      什么
Whoa.        What?
黑考斯在乐队吹竖笛 我也是
Heckles played clarinet in band, and I played clarinet.
他参加模型社 我也...
And he was in the scale modeler's club and I was...
虽然我们学校没有这个社 但是我真觉得模型很酷
well, there was no club, but I sure thought they were cool.
所以你们两个都是书呆子
So? You were both dorks.
有什么大不了的?
Big deal?
我只是觉得很诡异 黑考斯与我...
I just think it's weird, you know? Heckles and me...
黑考斯与我 我...
Heckles and me, me...
我与黑考斯...
Me and Heckles...
嘿 你们别吵了行不行!
Hey, would you knock it off!
啊!
Ah!
你整晚都在这里?
Have you been here all night?
看看这个
Look at this.
所有跟黑考斯交往过的女人
Pictures of all the women that Heckles went out with.
看看他写的 "薇薇安 太高"
Look what he wrote on them. "Vivian, too tall."
"玛斯 牙龈太露"
"Madge, big gums."
"太大声"
"Too loud."
"太聪明" "吃东西发出声音"
"Too smart." "Make snoise when she eats."
这 这就是我
This is, this is me.
这就是我的做法
This is what I do.
我会像他一样孤独终老
I'm gonna end up alone, just like he did.
钱德 黑考斯是个神经病
Chandler, Heckles was a nut case.
拜托 我们的人生轨迹是一样的
Our trains are on the same track, okay?
对 我是比他晚生30年
Yeah, sure, I'm coming up 30 years behind him
但终点都是一样的
but the stops are all the same.
苦逼镇...
Bitter Town...
孤独城 隐者村
Alone-ville, Hermit Junction!
好吧 知道我们该做什么吗 带你离开这里
All right, you know what we gotta do? We gotta get you outta here.
来吧 我请你吃早餐
Come on, I'll buy you breakfast, let's go.
要是我一直找不到另一半呢
What if I never find somebody?
或者更糟 万一我已经找到了
Or even worse, what if I've found her
但我却因为她的发音是"厚许"就把她甩了呢
but I dumped her because she pronounces it "supposably"?
钱德 好啦 你会找到另一半的
Chandler, come on, you're gonna find somebody.
你怎么知道
How do you know that? How?
我不知道 我只是想开导你
I don't know, I'm just trying to help you out.
看吧 你们将来都会离开我去结婚
You'll see, you guys are all gonna go off and get married
而我会孤寂而终
and I'm gonna end up alone.
你能答应我一件事吗?
Will you promise me something?
等你结婚后 过节时能不能请我去你家
When you're married, will you invite me over for holidays?
呃 我不知道到时候 我们在做什么
Well, I don't know. I don't know what we're gonna be doing.
我是指 万一我们得去她爸妈家过节呢
I mean, what if we're over at her folks' place?
好吧 我了解
Yeah, I understand.
你可以过来看超级碗嘛
You can come over and watch the Super Bowl.
每年都来 好吗
Every year, all right?
我不要这样的下场
You know what? I'm not gonna end up like this.
待会儿见 老兄
I'll see you, man.
"厚许"
"Supposably"
"厚许"!
"Supposably"!
他们去动物园了吗
Did they go to the zoo?
"厚许"吧...
"Supposably"...
嗨 是我
Hi, it's me.
我 的 天 哪 ！
Oh, my God!
珍妮丝? 你打给了珍妮丝?
Janice? You called Janice?
对 珍妮丝
Yes, Janice.
你们很难理解吗
Why is that so difficult for you to comprehend?
你还记得珍妮丝吧?
You remember Janice, right?
对 她聪明 漂亮 而且她真的很关心我
Yes, she was smart, she was pretty and she honestly cared about me.
珍妮丝是我最后的机会
Janice is my last chance to have somebody.
哈罗
Hello.
我 的 天 哪
Oh, my God!
天啊 她真是胖了不少
Jeez look how fat she got.
嘿 大伙儿都在!      嗨 珍妮丝
Hey it's everybody.        Hi, Janice.
珍妮丝 你已经...
Janice, you're...
是的 我有了
Yes, I am.
是不是...      是不是你的? 呵呵
Is it?        Is it yours? Ha!
少作梦了 钱德宾!
You wish, Chandler Bing.
我现在可是少妇了
You are looking at a married lady now.
噢
Oh.
是啊
Yeah.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
亲爱的 真抱歉
Aw, sweetie, I'm sorry.
你不能在电话上告诉我吗
You couldn't have told me about this over the phone?
要我错过你惊讶的表情? 才不要!
And what? Miss the expression on your face? Oh, no.
姑奶奶就喜欢找乐子
Janice likes to have her fun.
嘿 端秋 知道我们很久没玩什么了吗
Hey, Rache, you know what we haven't played in a while?
什么?      "把灯藏起来"
What?        "Hide the Lamp"
摩妮卡 算了吧
Hey, Monica, let it go.
你知道我对贝壳类过敏吗?
Did you know I'm allergic to shellfish?
那你只好去吃别的台灯了
Well, then, you'll just have to eat the other lamps.
啊哦 可怕的科学家来了
Uh-oh. Its scary scientist man.
好了 菲比 这些就是了
Okay, Phoebe, this is it.
在这手提箱中 我带来了真正的科学证据
In this briefcase I carry actual scientific facts.
可以算是一整箱的证据
A briefcase of facts, if you will.
其中有些化石是超过两亿年之久的
Some of these fossils are over 200 million years old.
听着 在你开始前 我先声明 我并不否定进化论
Okay, look, before you even start, I'm not denying evolution, okay?
我只是认为进化论是其中的一种可能性
I'm just saying that it's one of the possibilities.
菲比 这是唯一的可能性
It's the only possibility, Phoebe.
好吧 罗斯 你能不能稍稍敞开心胸
Okay, Ross, could you just open your mind, like, this much? Okay?
曾几何时
Wasn't there a time
世界上最聪明的人不也相信地球是平的吗
when the brightest minds in the world believe the Earth was flat?
追溯到50年之前
And, up until like what, 50 years ago
你们还认为原子是最小的粒子
you all thought the atom was the smallest thing
直到科学家击碎了原子 才弄出了一大堆鬼玩意儿
until you split it open, and this like, whole mess of crap came out.
你现在却告诉我 你是如此难以置信的自大到
Now, are you telling me that you are so unbelievably arrogant
完全不肯承认有那么一点点一丢丢的可能性
that you can't admit that there's a teeny, tiny possibility
你们科学家可能是错误的?
that you could be wrong about this?
是有那么...
There might be...
一点点...
a teeny...
一丢丢的...
tiny...
可能性
possibility.
我真不敢相信你屈服了
I cant believe you caved.
什么?      你放弃了你的整个信仰
What?        You just abandoned your whole belief system!
之前我虽然不认同你 但至少我还尊敬你
I mean, before, I didn't agree with you, but at least I respected you.
可是...
But...
明天你要怎样继续研究
How, how, how are you going to go into work tomorrow?
你要如何面对其他科学家
How, how are you going to face the other science guys?
你要如何面对你自己 噢...
How, how are you going to face yourself? Oh...
真欢乐 有谁饿了
That was fun. So who's hungry?
我
I am.
我也是 我去拿外套
Me too. Let me just get my coat.
出什么事了      没事
What happened?        Okay, all right.
这是意外 我发誓
It was an accident, I swear, all right?
我正在穿外套 那台灯 就破了
I was putting on my jacket and the thing and the lamp and it broke.
哦 拜托 摩妮卡! 你一向讨厌我的灯!
Oh, please, Monica! You've always hated my lamp!
而突然间 它就奇迹般地破了?
And now, all of a sudden, it's just magically, it's just broken?
菲比 你告诉她
Phoebe, tell her?
我没看到 因为我正在穿外套
Okay, I didn't see it, cuz I was putting on my jacket.
不过我想相信你
But uh, I want to believe you.
钱德 摩妮卡打破了我的贝壳台灯
Hey, Chandler, Monica just broke my seashell lamp.
真棒
Neat.
我会孤独终老!
I'm gonna die alone!
好吧 算你赢
Okay, you win.
钱德 你不会孤寂而终的啦
Chandler, you are not gonna die alone.
珍妮丝本来是我最有把握的 好吗?
Janice was my safety net, okay?
现在我只好去养条蛇了
And now I have to get a snake.
这又是为什么
Uh-huh. Why is that?
如果我会成为孤独的老头子 我就需要有个东西
If I'm gonna be an old, lonely man, Im gonna need a thing.
像是依靠
You know, a hook.
就像地铁上那个吃自己脸的家伙
Like that guy on the subway who eats his own face.
所以我想要成为"养蛇的疯老头"
So I figure I'll be "Crazy Man With A Snake"
惊蛇郎君
Crazy-Snake-Man.
然后我会弄更多的蛇 当成我的子女
Then I'll get more snakes, call them my babies
小孩都不敢经过我的门口
kids will walk past my place, they will run!
他们会尖叫 "快跑啊!惊蛇郎君来啦!"
"Run away from Crazy-Snake-Man!" they'll shout!
你得想开点
You've got to get over this, okay?
你不会孤苦伶仃的
You're not gonna end up alone.
我当然会
Of course lam.
我甩掉了所有疯狂到愿意跟我交往的女孩
I reject anyone who's crazy enough to actually go out with me
然后我开始抱怨这世上根本没有好女孩
and then I bitch about the fact that there aren't any great women out there.
钱德 你所描述的
Chandler, you have just described
其实就跟我们交往过的所有男人一样
virtually every man that we've ever gone out with.
是啊
Yeah.
你不是异类 你只是个平常人
You are not a freak. You're a guy.
她说的没错 你和其他人没什么不同
She's right. She's right. You're no different than the rest of them.
等等 不 他不一样
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Yes he is.
你完全不同      很糟吗
You are totally different.        In a bad way?
不 亲爱的 是好的不一样
No, honey, in a wonderful way.
现在你知道自己要什么了
You know what you want now.
大部分的男人压根儿没明白
Most guys don't even have a clue.
你准备好承担风险了
You're ready to take risks
准备好接受伤害了 愿意与人亲近了
you're ready to be vulnerable and intimate with someone.
对 你不会孤苦伶仃的
Yeah, you're not gonna end up alone.
钱德 你打给珍妮丝 这说明你渴望与人白头偕老
Chandler, you called Janice. That's how much you wanted to be with someone!
你做到了      你办到了
You've made it!        You're there!
你准备好做出承诺了
You are ready to make a commitment!
这我还不能确定
Whoa! Don't know about that.
看你拿了什么
Wow, what you got there?
又是个不属于你的 你又想摔坏的东西?
Something else that's not yours that you can break?
不是
No.
我知道你喜欢这个 我要你收下
Um, I know you like this, and I want you to have it.
我想它在我们公寓里会很搭
I think it'll look good in our apartment.
谢谢你
Thank you.
没关系啦
That's fine.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
知道了你们一定会很高兴 明晚我有个约会
Well, you'll all be pleased to know that I have a date tomorrow night.
我的同事艾莉森 人很不错
This woman Allison from work, she is great.
她既漂亮又聪明 我一直...
She's pretty, she's smart, and I've been...
没约她出来 因为她有个...
holding off asking her out in the past, because she has a...
硕大无比的头
unusually large head.
但我再也不想因为这种事阻止我了
But I'm not going to let that stuff hang me up anymore.
这才对嘛
All right.
看看我 成熟了
Look at me, I'm growing.
纪念册是不能回收的吧?
Hey, you can't recycle yearbooks, can you?
这个我要了
I'll take that.
你要他的纪念册?
You want his yearbook?
是啊 有人说了他的好话
Yeah, yeah. Some people said some nice things about him.
应该保管好
Somebody should have it.
天呐 这真的很奇怪
Gosh, this is so weird.
他的一生都在这间公寓里度过 现在人去楼空
I mean, his whole life was in this apartment， and now it'sgone.
我想我们应该为黑考斯先生默哀一会儿
You know, I think it'd be nice if we just took a few moments for Mr.Heckles.
他曾经确实是个挺麻烦的人 但他毕竟是位老先生
I mean, he was kind of a pain, he was, but he was a person.
怎么了
What?
你们全都会下地狱
You're all going to hell.
其实没那么大啦!
It's really not that big.
你要带走那个?      必须的
Taking that with you, huh?        Oh, yeah.
嘿 一起走吗
Hey, you coming?
嗯 待会儿
Yeah, in a second.
再见了 黑考斯先生
Goodbye, Mr.Heckles.
我们会尽量安静点
We'll try to keep it down.
我完全学无所用
Oh, My major was useless.
我是说
I mean
报纸上什么时候看得到 "征求哲学家"的
how often do you look in the classifieds and see "Philosopher Wanted"?
呵呵 是啊
Heh, heh. Sure.
尼玛 好大一个头!
My God, that's a big head!
办公室里看起来没这么大 也许是灯光的缘故
It didn't look this big in the office. Maybe it's the lighting.
我的头在公司一定像高尔夫球那么小
My head must look like a golf ball at work.
好吧 别管这些
All right, don't get hung up on it.
快点 列出你喜欢她的五点
Quick, quick. List five things you like about her.
笑容可掬 穿着有品
Nice smile, good dresser
大头 大头 还是大头!
Big head, big head, big head!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧